kasanovaonline.com 2010-03-08

# Privacy | Kasanova Online

## Privacy

KASANOVAONLINE.COM is very concerned with protecting your personal integrity when you use KASANOVAONLINE.COM. This Privacy Policy states how we handle your personal information. We are very cautious that the personal information that you give to us is handled in such a way that your personal integrity will not be infringed. With this Privacy Policy we aim to provide you with information regarding the technical handling of your personal information. 

The Privacy Policy is incorporated in the Terms of Use Agreement and by approving the Terms of Use Agreement you also approve of this Privacy Policy. Therefore, when you ratify the conditions of the Terms of Use Agreement you also consent to granting us the authority to collect, use, process and disclose information relating to you in accordance with this Privacy Policy and according to applicable laws. If you do not agree to all of these terms and conditions, you should not use KASANOVAONLINE.COM and provide us with any information. 

All personal information submitted by KASANOVAONLINE.COM users such as name, address, email address and age etc. is collected by us and can be used to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to, but not limited to KASANOVAONLINE.COM, events, contests and special offers. 

In compliance with the general practice of, for example, commercial Websites we also collect information about you that can not directly be referred to you. This type of information includes for example the IP-address of the computer you use, profile information, aggregate user data and browser type. This type of information is logged both from Members and visitors to KASANOVAONLINE.COM. The collected information is used to further develop the services provided by us and make them more user-friendly and better adapted to the needs and tastes of the KASANOVAONLINE.COM users. The non-personally-identifiable information may be used for improvements and administration of the Website and, it may also be used to analyze trends, to follow the movements of users around the services or to gather demographic information about the users as a collective. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties in order to provide more relevant services and advertisements adapted to the KASANOVAONLINE.COM users. However, we will not use the non- personally-identifiable information collected to market directly to the specific user. User IP-addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. 

In order to follow and analyze the movements and interests of our users, we use pixel tags that are tiny graphic images that tell us what parts of the KASANOVAONLINE.COM services that have been visited. The pixel tags are also used to measure how effective the searches are that the users perform on our services and they can also be used to enable us to send emails in a format each user can read. Pixel tags are also used by us to trace whether emails have been opened and we do this to protect our users from unwanted messages. All pixel tag information is stored in a secure database. 

Information relating to Member Profiles such as pictures and username is displayed to other KASANOVAONLINE.COM users in order to make user interaction in the Community easier. However, the Member`s full name is never directly revealed to other Members. 

The email addresses collected by us from the Members may be used to send news about the services such as updates and newsletters, etc. The emails sent by us may contain a "click-through URL" link that leads to contents on the KASANOVAONLINE.COM. When the URL's are clicked they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. The "click-through URL" is tracked by us in order for us to make our services more effective and better adapted to the user`s interests. Therefore, if you do not want to be tracked by us, we kindly ask you not to click any links in emails sent to you by us. 

As stated in the Terms of Use Agreement we and/or our partners may sponsor promotions, sweepstakes or contests on the KASANOVAONLINE.COM services. When participating in any of these events you may be asked for personal information such as your name or email address. In some cases you may also be asked to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. If this is the case it will be clearly stated at the point of your participation who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement or what regulation will apply. 

USE OF COOKIES 

Cookies are small files that are placed on your hard drive and they are used by us in order to improve the quality of the services we offer you. The cookies help to manage sessions on KASANOVAONLINE.COM by remembering your Member preferences, and ensure that you do not continually see the same advertisements. If you want to use KASANOVAONLINE.COM properly, cookies must be enabled. Please observe that the information stored in cookies is not linked to any personally identifiable information. 

We allow third party advertisers that place their advertisements in connection with our services to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own Privacy Policies and not to this Privacy Policy. 

LINKS 

KASANOVAONLINE.COM may contain links to Websites managed by third parties. These Websites have got nothing to do with us and therefore we accept no responsibility for the contents and/ or the privacy policies on these sites. Since this Privacy Policy only governs information directly connected to KASANOVAONLINE.COM, we strongly suggest that when you link to another site you take time to review their Privacy Policy. 

COMMENTING OR POSTING ON KASANOVAONLINE.COM 

It is important that you have in mind that whenever you post information or comment on something, that it can be accessed by others. This means that you may for example get unsolicited communications. We do not take any responsibility for any personal information that you choose to post on our services. Neither do we accept any responsibility for the consequences. 

Trig merely provides a space for its users to exchange and express their own opinions. In accordance with the terms of use, you are entirely responsible and liable for all Content that you post on Trig. We do not guarantee that the Content posted on the forum on Trig is accurate, reliable or up to date. Any reliance upon the Content published on the forum is at the user`s own risk. The content is published "AS-IS" and may not represent Our official view and opinion. 

It is not possible for Us to review the Content before it is posted and We assume no responsibility or liability for any posted Content. It is very important that you report any illegal or inappropriate Content that you become aware of to KASANOVAONLINE.COM or by clicking on "Report Inappropriate Content". 

COMMUNICATIONS TO NON-MEMBERS 

When using the KASANOVAONLINE.COM "Send an invitation" feature, you are asked to give the email address of a friend. When you choose to give us one of your friend's email address, we will automatically send your friend an invitation to join the KASANOVAONLINE.COM Community. Your friend's email address is then stored in order for us to be able to automatically add your friend to your friend list when she/he signs up. We also send reminder notifications of your invitation. 

CORRECTING/UPDATING OR REMOVING INFORMATION 

Members of KASANOVAONLINE.COM have access to their KASANOVAONLINE.COM account by logging on and clicking on the "Login" page and there personal information contained in their account may be updated or removed. Changes can be made at any time. 

SECURITY 

The safety of your personal information is a high priority for us. All Member accounts are secured by passwords. The information on your account can only be accessed by you and our employees that need access in order to fulfill their job functions, such as technical staff and customer service personnel. Although we have taken great measures to protect your privacy, we can not guarantee the security of your account information. Therefore, it is important that you take precautions to protect your personal data by, for example, choosing a password consisting both numbers and letters, and by changing your password often. Of course you must also use a secure web browser. Technical failure, unauthorized use or entry, and other factors may lead to a security breach of member information at any time. 

SHARING AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT 

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by us, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of Members, of the public and visitors of KASANOVAONLINE.COM. We reserve the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of the Website or the Company or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. 

We do not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers. To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with our entities that will safeguard it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. There are also times when it may be advantageous for us to make certain personal information about you available to companies that we have a strategic relationship with or that perform work for us to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us to process information, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your personal information in accordance with our policies. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to purchase products, have products delivered to you, receive customer service, provide us with feedback to improve our products and services, or access certain services, offers, and contents on KASANOVAONLINE.COM. 

PRIVACY OF CHILDREN 

Children are not authorized to use KASANOVAONLINE.COM and we recommend under-aged (under the age of 18) not to send personal information to KASANOVAONLINE.COM. If you are under-age you may only use KASANOVAONLINE.COM if you have the permission of your parents or your legal guardian. This requirement is clearly posted during the registration process. 

CHANGES IN OUR PRIVACY POLICY 

From time to time, we may make changes in our Privacy Policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are, so you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A user is bound by any minor changes to the Privacy Policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted. If, however, we are going to use Members' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify by posting a notice on KASANOVAONLINE.COM for 30 days. 

CONTACTING THE WEB SITE 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: info@KASANOVAonline.com
